

Shashank Bhattacharya

Front End Developer

New Delhi, India

+91 8447997069

shwshank3@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/ shashank-bhattacharya-58aa6879/

github.com/Shwshank

shwshank.github.io

EDUCATION-

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science - AKTU

March 2010 - March 2014

Intermediate - CBSE India 2009-2010

SKILLS -

- ∘ React, Redux, Jest, Enzyme
- Preact, Next, Webpack
- ∘ Typescript, HTML5, CSS3
- ES6, Data Visualization
- Node, Express, Mongoose
- ∘ S3, EC2, Firebase
- Serverless
- o CICD, Git, Jenkins
- Salesforce Certified Administrator

SUMMARY -

Javascript | React | Data Visualization | Full stack 60 - 40 (Frontend - Backend)

Ambitious computer enthusiast with strong experience in building pixel-perfect interactive data visualization web apps and an active contributor to opensource.

I've worked on scalable, single-solution driven diverse projects Most of the time I am involved in implementing optimal user experience for the frontend and sometimes developing backend features.

EXPERIENCE -

Front End Developer

R Systems, Noida

Dec-2019 present

Currently working on data visualization and real-time asset tracking, health monitoring dashboard. Worked on SEO optimized, dynamic content generated server-side rendered Ecommerce platform.

Front End Developer

Quality Council of India, New Delhi

Jan-2017 Nov-2019

Involved in developing & maintaining in-house data visualized platforms and web apps. Developed scalable solutions to execute huge traffic oriented platforms with varying network coverage.

Salesforce Administrator

HCL, Bengaluru

April 2015- Jan 2017

I was part of a team providing SFDC administrator support to clients, resolving real-time queries, designing and developing SFDC organization structures.

Co-Founder, Developer

Innovative Medegus, New Delhi

March 2014-Jan 2015

Co-Founded and developed an online healthcare platform to facilitate patient management. Being an early-stage startup I was able to get myself involved in all of the phases of SDLC.